lottosend.org 2016-06-13

# Lottosend | We Take Our Privacy Responsibilities Seriously | Lottsend

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Lottosend.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the Lottosend.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Lottosend.com. 

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, however it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

#### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance the User experience. Users’ web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

#### How we use collected information

Lottosend.com may collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
  * To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * To improve our Site we may use feedback Users provide to improve our products and services. 
  * To process payments we may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order exclusively to provide service for that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 
  * To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to send Users information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, the User will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User should desire to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email to enable such an action.

#### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Users’ personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users takes place over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

#### Sharing personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that that the appropriate permissions have been provided. 

#### Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

Lottosend.com is not structured to accept Users under the age of 18, therefore, we do not intend to collect or maintain personal information from anyone we know to be under the age of 18. 

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Lottosend.com maintains the option to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Users acknowledge and agree that it is their responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site please contact us at: [Support@Lottosend.com](mailto:support@Lottosend.com)

_This document was last updated on July 30, 2013_
